A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.36 (A2011) FA496
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.36 (A2011)
1998-2009
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA496
13.1 Cubic Feet 10 standard record storage boxes, R3925-R3934
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 2011.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 20 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Separated Materials
Special Formats (digital media) have been separated from the body of the collection. All pertinent items are assigned a unique separation number, as noted. Requests to access open special formats should reference the unique separation number.
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program, with some materials arranged by the RF traditional series numbers.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Scope and Contents
Grant administration files and related material.
- AC.2011.037: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2001-2009; AC.2011.037; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 standard record storage boxes, R3925-R3929.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 6.55 Cubic Feet 5 record storage boxes
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted - Open in 2026
    - RESIDENT (Aaron, Henry J.), 2003-2006 (Box R3925)
      Restricted - Open in 2027
    - RESIDENT (Alexander, Bobby C.) (CO-RESIDENT: Fortuny-Loret De Mola, Patricia), 2003-2005 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Altman, Dennis), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Ammann, Klaus) (CO-RESIDENT: Gressel, Jonathan), 2003-2008 (Box R3925)
      Restricted - Open in 2029
    - RESIDENT (Andrews, Penelope E.), 2002-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Arnold, Robert F.) (CO-RESIDENT: Mortimer, Roz), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Ashrafi, Mukaddima), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Bacon, David), 2003-2005 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Banaji, Mahzarin R.), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Beoku-Betts, Josephine Antoinette), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Berde, Charles Benjamin) (CO-RESIDENT: Schechter, Neil L.), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Bhattacharyya, Subhabrata) (CO-RESIDENT: Bose, Brinda), 2003-2005 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Blachly, James T.), 2002-2005 (Box R3925)
    - Resident, 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Bogart, Anne Dean), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Boxer, Diana) (CO-RESIDENT: Gritsenko, Elena S.), 2003-2006 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Bresnick, Martin I.), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Burbick, Joan S.), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Burgan, Mary Alice), 2003-2005 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Canovan, Margaret Evelyn), 2003-2006 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Carlson, Ann M.) (CO-RESIDENT: Strom, Mary Ellen), 2004-2005 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Carroll, Mary Ellen), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Cole, Henri R.), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Crutchfield, Robert D.), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (Das, Ashok K.) (CO-RESIDENT: Perez, Silvana), 2003-2004 (Box R3925)
    - RESIDENT (De George, Richard T.), 2003-2007 (Box R3926)
      Restricted - Open in 2028
    - RESIDENT (de Gruchy, John W.), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Decker, John Paul), 2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Del Conde, Teresa), 2002-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Deyo, Richard A.), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Dickson, Marsha A.) (CO-RESIDENT: Littrell, Mary Ann), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Dudziak, Mary L.), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Erasmus, Garth Thomas), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Eshleman, Clayton), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Feige, Edgar L.), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Femenias, Blenda Beatriz), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Forgas, Joseph Paul), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Garti, Nissim), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Garza, Carmen Lomas), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Gorman, Paul Timothy), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Gossman, Patricia Ann), 2004-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Green, Michael D.), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Guendelman, Sylvia R.), 2003-2006 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Gurganus, Allan), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Hagen, Daron Aric), 2003-2006 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Hagendoorn, Louk) (CO-RESIDENT: Sniderman, Paul M.), 2003-2005 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Hake, Sabine), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Hermann, Tamar Sara), 2001-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Herring, George C.), 2003-2009 (Box R3926)
      Restricted - Open in 2030
    - RESIDENT (Hofmeyr, George Justus), 2003-2004 (Box R3926)
    - RESIDENT (Holmes, Janet), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Honey, Michael Keith), 2002-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Horwitz, Morton J.), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Irwin, Terence Henry), 2003-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Jaffe, Jacqueline Anne) (CO-RESIDENT: Wolfswinkel, Rolf), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Jaffe, Robert Loren), 2004-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Kallings, Lars O.), 2003-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Kecskes, Istvan), 2003-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (King, John N.), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Kraut, Richard), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Krog, Antjie), 2002-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Kruger, Lou-Marie), 2003-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Kubovy, Michael) (CO-RESIDENT: Tyler, Christopher W.), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Kuo, Alex), 2002-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Lemon, Ralph S.), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Lerman, Zvi), 2003-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Lieb, Michael), 2002-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Light, Ivan), 2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Lobachev, Sergey Vladimirovich), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Loppert, Max Jeremy), 2002-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Lu, Xiaobo), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Madison, D. Soyini), 2003-2005 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Maidana, Elena Silvia) (CO-RESIDENT: Millan, Monica), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Makhubu, Lydia Phindile), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Mandal, Somdatta), 2003-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Martin-Acena, Pablo), 2002-2004 (Box R3927)
    - RESIDENT (Mathews, John Alwyn), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Medina, Pablo F.), 2002-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Meijer, Frederik Gerrit), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Miller, David A.), 2003-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Milner, Helen V.), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Moorefield, Virgil E.), 2003-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Murray, Anne Firth), 2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Murray, Christina M.) (CO-RESIDENT: Simeon, Richard E. B.), 2003-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Naumkin, Vitaly V.), 2003-2006 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Neipris, Janet), 2003-2006 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Neuberger, Julia), 2003-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Newman, Barbara Jane), 2003-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Olupona, Jacob K.), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Orlin, Lena Cowen), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Ornelas, Carlos), 2003-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Panaite, Viorel), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Pentecost, Claire), 2004-2005 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Perdue, Theda), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Porter, Toni B.), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Pottlitzer, Joanne), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Rabossi, Eduardo Antonio), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Ramalho, Jos‚ Ricardo G.P.), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Rankin, William Wright), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Rao, Nitya), 2003-2009 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Reinhartz, Adele), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Ritchie, Jan Elizabeth), 2003-2004 (Box R3928)
    - RESIDENT (Robinson, Lillian S.), 2002-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Robson, Catherine), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Rosenzweig, Morris), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Royal, Charles P.), 2003-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Sarwar, Zeba Beena), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Scott, Stephen Allen), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Shamieh, Betty), 2004-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Shatin, Judith), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Shirley, Dennis Lynn), 2004-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Sivan, Hagith), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Skloot, Floyd), 2003-2006 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Solari, Ana), 2001-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Spelke, Elizabeth S.), 2003-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Spickard, Paul Russell), 2003-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Sriram, Chandra L.), 2003-2006 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Staunton, Irene Anne), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Stephens, Robert W.), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Stoller, Nancy Elaine), 2002-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Suny, Ronald Grigor), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Szahaj, Andrej Jaroslaw), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Thomson, Peter Pearmain), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Trethewey, Natasha), 2003-2006 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Tufte, Thomas), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Tuite, Clara), 2003-2005 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (van Zyl, John Andrew), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Wade, Jan L.), 2002-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Walker, James W.), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Wight, Gail M.), 2002-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Wilson, Douglas L.), 2003-2004 (Box R3929)
    - RESIDENT (Zabus, Chantal), 2003-2007 (Box R3929)
- AC.2011.042: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 2000-2006; AC.2011.042; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 standard record storage boxes, R3930-R3932.
  - Bellagio Study and Conference Center, 120; 3.94 Cubic Feet 3 record storage boxes
    - CONFERENCE: Application of Molecular Pharmacology for Post-testicular Activities, 2001-2005 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Constructing a New Cross-national Architecture for Labor Market Statistics, 2001-2003 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Cultural Agency in the Americas, 2001-2002 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Decentralization and the Environment: Assessing Participation for Rio+10, 2000-2005 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Decentralization and the Environment: Assessing Participation for Rio+10 - Team File, 2000-2005 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Diversity and Citizenship Education in Multicultural Societies, 2001-2005 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Economic Agendas in Civil Wars: Assessing the Prospects for a Global Regulatory Framework, 2001-2002 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Extending the Boundaries of Democracy: Evaluating Two Decades of Education Reform and Inclusion, 2002-2003 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Female Circumcision: Multicultural Perspectives, 2001-2006 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Globalization and Sites of lntranational Transactions: The Erosion of Borders and the Challenges for the European Union, 2001-2002 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Green Mapmakers Global Gathering, 2001-2005 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Health System Productivity, 2000-2002 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Impacts of Globalization on Urban Development, 2001-2006 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: Innovative Experiences in Philanthropic Leadership Development in Latin America and among Latino Populations in the U.S., 2001-2002 (Box R3930)
    - CONFERENCE: lnnovia: Patient Experience and the New Technologies in Health Care, 2001-2003 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: New Forms of Democracy?: The Reform and Transformation of Democratic Institutions, 2001-2004 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: New Forms of Urbanization: Conceptualizing and Measuring Human Settlement in the Twenty-first Century, 2001-2004 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Oil and Conflict, 2001-2003 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Progress and Prospects for Place-based Randomized Trials, 2001-2003 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Proteolytic Machines in Human Disease, 2000-2002 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Science and Ethics: Experience and Challenges in the United States and in Iran, 2001-2003 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Soil Fertility Degradation in Africa: Leveraging Long-Term Solutions to a Long-Term Problem, 2001-2003 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Thomas Jefferson, Rights, and the Contemporary World, 2000-2002 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Transcending Post-Seattle Angst, 2000-2002 (Box R3931)
    - CONFERENCE: Workers' Rights/Women's Rights: Women in the Global Economy, 2001-2002 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: Conversations in Choreography: 4th Session, 2001-2004 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: Creativity and Dissent, 2000-2002 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: Demography and Health in Africa, 2002-2003 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: Development of the Communication for Social Change Curriculum, 2002-2003 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: Diaries: A Theater Project, 2000-2002 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: EU Enlargement and Agricultural Policies in Poland, 2001-2002 (Box R3931)
    - BC TEAM: Global RF Human Resources Workshop, 2002 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Health Equity Strategy Meeting, 2002 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Identifying Competencies for Communication for Social Change: A Global Perspective, 2001-2002 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Indigenous Women's History of Colonial Domestic Work in Vanuatu, 2001-2003 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Margaret Garner - An Opera in Two Acts, 2002 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Philanthropy Workshop - Review and Strategic Planning, 2001-2002 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Red de Veedores, or Citizen Watch Net of Venezuela: An Experience of Research Action, 2001-2003 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Rockin' Las Americas: The Global Politics of Rock in Latin America, 2001-2004 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Sound of Falling Light, 2001-2003 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Strengthening Nationally Competitive Scholarships, 2002-2004 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Tribal Transitions: Assessing 50 Years of Cultural Change in Arunachal Pradesh, India, 2001-2003 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Women in Informal Employment: Globalizing and Organizing Steering Committee Meeting, 2001-2003 (Box R3932)
    - BC TEAM: Women Writing Africa: Western/Sahel Region, 2002 (Box R3932)
- AC.2011.043: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1998-2009; AC.2011.043; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 standard record storage boxes, R3933-R3934.
  - Fellowships (F), AC.2011.043.1; 2.63 Cubic Feet 2 record storage boxes
    - F 98038 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) MAZHANGARA, EDWARD P., 1998-2009 (Box R3933)
    - F 99044 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) MAKAUDZE, EPHIAS, 1999-2008 (Box R3933)
    - F 99047 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) NIGHT, GERTRUDE, 1998-2006 (Box R3933)
    - F 99053 - (UGANDA) (F-AS) MULUMBA, LUKMAN NAGAYA, 1997-2007 (Box R3933)
    - F 99046 - (ZIMBABWE) (F-AS) NYIKA, MICHAEL ANDREW, 1998-2007 (Box R3934)
    - F 99072 - (KENYA) (F-AS) OKELLO, JULIUS JUMA, 1998-2006 (Box R3934)